

# Mark Salvaña

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER, CONSULTANT



### **Age:** 32

### Mobile/Whatsapp/Viber:

+639198602609 (PH)

Email: email@marksalvana.com Addess: Mandaluyong, Metro Manila

Philippines, 1550

Website: https://marksalvana.com



twitter.com/lBigByte



linkedin.com/in/marksalvana/



github.com/marksalvana

## **Education**

Mapua Institute of Technology Computer-Science (UG) 2012-2017

**Philippines Science High School** 2004-2008

### Stacks

### Languages

PHP, Javascript, HTML, CSS3, MySQL, Svelte, MongoDB, Typescript

### **Frameworks**

Laravel, React, SvelteKit Express, Node, Tailwind

### **Platforms**

Wordpress, OctoberCMS, Drupal, Zoho Creator

### **Character Reference**

### Miguel Dela Rosa

Director Operations-GlobalWebforce (+63) 917 516 6897

### Mae De Sesto

Manager - MRC Tasmania 03 6221 0999 (AU)

### **Culver Songalia**

President - Entrepreneurs Accounting Academy +639178387144 (PH)

### **About**

Experienced and passionate web developer with more than 10 years experience. While it may feel a bit self-serving to talk about my accomplishments, I genuinely strive to make a positive impact through my work. I am dedicated to refining my skills, embracing challenges, and making a difference in the ever-evolving landscape of software development

# Skills/Expertise

### 🚣 Full-Stack Web Development

Skilled in Frontend and Backend Development using Laravel, Sveltekit, Wordpress, October, Shopify

### Al Automation & Development

Knowledge response, Chatbot development & Model tuning using LangChain and GPT-3 | GPT 4

### API Development

Build scalable APIs for your PWA or mobile aps using PHP, NodeJS, Eloquent, MongoDB and MySQL

# Mentorship & Consultancy

Solutions Consultancy in Business Process Automation, Software development & Digital Marketing

# **Experience**

Please check marksalvana.com for the projects I was involved in during my stay on the companies mentioned below.

### **GlobalWebforce** Australia

Senior Web Developer 2020-2023

As a senior full-stack web developer at GWF, I oversee the entire project lifecycle, from scoping to support. I propose solutions, allocate resources, assign tasks, develop, test, and create comprehensive reports.

### Tech&Design

Proprietor 2018-2020 Following my tenure at EAA, I took the entrepreneurial path and founded Tech&Design, a web development and design business specialized in crafting websites and delivering comprehensive IT

# **Entrepreneurs**

### **Accounting Academy**

Operations Manager 2016-2018

**IT Supervisor** 2015-2016

Senior Web Developer 2012-2015

**Graphic Artist** 2010-2012

and digital marketing consulting services.

At EAA, I successfully held multiple roles from Operations Manager to Sales & Marketing Supervisor, Web Designer, and Graphic Artist. My adaptability, coupled with a passion for continuous learning, allows me to thrive in dynamic environments and contribute effectively to thecompany specially in the fields of Marketing, Web Development, and IT.